There's a hundred
and four days of summer vacation
And school comes
along just to end it
So the annual
problem for our generation
Is finding a
good way to spend it
Life ain't easy
Building a rocket
or fighting a mummy
Or climbing up
the Eiffel Tower
Discovering
something that doesn't exist
Hey，Giving a
monkey a shower
Serpent
tidal waves
Creating nanobots
and locating Frankenstein's brain
Said Julie
Finding a
dodo bird
Painting a continent or driving her sister insane
Said Phoebe
As you can see
There's a whole lot of stuff to do before school starts this fall
Said Clarice
So stick with us
Cause Phineas and
Ferb are gonna do it all
媽媽，飛哥和小佛他們又開始喇
飛哥與小佛十大最佳金曲
PFT，我們正在進行現場直播
歡迎節目主持人
兩位在道德、
倫理和哲學上分出極端位置的
漢斯杜芬舒斯博士
以及弗朗西斯莫萊爾管隊長
大家好啊
對，我們在後台已經先休息了一會
等等，我要回到剛剛
你的名字叫法蘭西斯，史思，斯文的思
斯文的思，不是那個西施，不是
是法蘭西斯，很有男子氣概的名字
弗蘭西斯？
沒錯
好了，我們不是來討論我的名字
我們來是因為全世界的孩子都上網投票
給他們最喜歡的飛哥小佛音樂片段
我們要一一宣布，首先公布第十名
準備好了嗎，杜博士？
法蘭弗朗西斯，好聽，對，真有氣感
所以讓你們叫我莫萊管隊長
各位女士、先生
凱迪斯和他最好的朋友史黛西
You gotta bang
your Betty Bongos
And bring your
Betty Bass Guitar
And whip the
Betty Backbeat
You'll go
Betty Bangstar
So drop your
boring baggage
And come with
Missy Ting and Crash
There's a
Betty Bandwagon
Going to a
Ready for
the fadis
Ready for the f
你猜，你弟他們現在在做什麼？
管他呢
怎麼樣？
喜歡這首歌嘛？
老杜，太吵喇
現在的小孩都喜歡音樂吵吵鬧鬧的
好，接下來這首老一輩的觀眾一定喜歡
你知道路人是怎麼説你的嗎？
你的話不太靠得住，噢，第九名的歌是…
把你當朋友我才這麼説的
沒錯，你們懂㗎
跟着音樂走，小佛
在我旁邊的是辛迪
攝影棚裏非常活潑的觀眾
快啲收火庫幣啦
現在呢，主持棒交給我那位犯罪的夥伴
意思當然不是説我們一起犯罪
我從來就…
開爾，大字報誰寫的？
Chimmy Taim
什麼？這是什麼東西啊？
竟然是打字機？
猜我上次看別人用打字機是什麼時候？
是1987年，這個…
你應該知道看這個節目的孩子
從沒有見過打字機，對吧？
經費有限，所以你就去古董商店…
繼續吧，第八名，波達索
你是用錄像帶
而不是用底片或者是皮影戲
So you're saying
that you don't have rhythm？
But listen what
you're doing right there
With that stamp
and a book you got a real nice hook
Sounds to me like
you got rhythm to spare
I have no idea
what you're talking about
I've got as much
rhythm as that chair
What happened to
me was a tragedy
But I don't have
to be a millionaire
Look， I got a
sweet deal going on here
I got all the
books that I can read
All these sweet
old ladies in this carpet from the 80s
What more could
a librarian need？
Shh
Besides I ain'
t got rhythm
No，I ain't
got rhythm
Said I ain'
t got rhythm
I ain't got rhythm
You're kidding me
right？
Don't you see
what you were doing right then？
That's a wicked
groove you were starting to move
Mister，you got
rhythm times ten
I think perhaps
that you're not listening
I find it
tedious to repeat
It's no big crime
I just can'
t keep time
I'm telling you
I lost the beat
I don't need my
face on tshirts
Or hit a
power chord guitar
They were
screaming my name
I guess it'
s a shame
But I don't need
to be a rock star
Said I ain'
t got rhythm
No
I ain't got rhythm
Said I ain'
t got rhythm
I ain't got rhythm
He got rhythm
Sounds like
rhythm to me
He got rhythm
Seems like
they all agree
But you're laying
down some funky sick oppression
He got rhythm
But you
got that beat
Look at them they'
re stomping their feet
He got rhythm
It's time for you
to rock a brand new generation
Gonna rock a
brand new generation
Because I ain'
t got rhythm
快去加入樂團吧
看看我
再看這個，注意看好了
嘿，我抓到節奏喇
嘿，總之呢
我也不能空着手來上這個特別的節目
所以我帶來了一些小禮物讓大家分享
你看喇
音樂錄像帶《終結者》
當我還是小男孩
我父母從來不准我看音樂錄像帶的
夠喇，我們沒有時間聽你恐怖的背景故事
那也許我該説個恐怖的前景故事囖
不用，那種故事更沒有道理
不需要道理，我有巨獸車
Thanks for all
the care and love you give
Not to
mention the meals
Sometimes I
get kinda nervous
Emma
forget to tell
you how I feel
Shooby doo
shooby doo
I'm a little
high strung
It's just
because I'm young
Mama，I adore ya
And I'll do
anything for you
弗朗西斯不知道的是
這根本就不是什麼音樂錄像帶終結者
它是「音樂錄像帶控制思想終結者」
剛剛我正在説…
思想…
控制我的鯨魚？
難道…
我説的不是嗎？
就在那邊
看到沒？
我沒有吹牛，接下來播放第六名
凱蒂斯，你是不是又靠近野生防風草喇？
是啊，你一定要看看飛哥跟小波做的好事
又怎麼了？
太感人喇，凱迪斯，太感人喇
真是…
真是太精彩喇
我要用它當我的手機鈴聲，現在
我要畀現場年輕嘅觀眾一個驚喜
我請嚟嘅這位貴賓，有他專屬嘅主題曲
Dooby do
嘿，泰瑞呢？
他正在上音樂錄像帶特別節目當嘉賓
好，很正點
密探阿泰，我想大家都想知道
今晚節目中你都在想些什麼呢？
噢，謝謝光臨
現在係個好機會
介紹下一段音樂錄像帶，接下來嘅是
觀眾票選第五名的作品
Now somebody
anybody
everybody scream
Squirrels on my pants，That girl's got some serious squirrels in her pants，Squirrels on my pants，Tell me what's making you jump like that，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels on my pants，Squirrels
Step right over
and watch me put it down
S to the A
to the M，to the P
Ooh，you got
that going
watering
your plants
S I M P
squirrels in my pants
How can I qualify
for government grants？
S I M P
squirrels in my pants
Hypnotize me
put me in a trance
S I M P
squirrels in my pants
Gallivanting
in Florence
living in France
S I M P
squirrels in my pants
S，I.M，P.
There's
something in my cajun
You know
it ain't ass
S，I.M，P.
squirrels in my pants
Yeah， proletarian bourgeoisie
Baby you don't
need an academic degree
Everybody
smellin' my potpourri
You're on
the ground
Cause you know I
got it going on
S to the A
to the M
to the P，S to the A
to the M，to the P
If your
pockets are empty
get a cash advance
S to the A
to the M，to the P
If you're
losing your head
get yourself
implants，S to the A
to the M，to the P
If you're
wrestling the bands
then you ain'
t got a chance
S to the A
to the M，to the P
Old Uncle Freddie
just rips and rips
It ain't
about love
about romance
I got squirrels in my pants
你千萬不要走開，節目回來
我們要公布前四名的歌曲
外加讓三周地區成為奴隸的特別錄像帶
我是説…
雕刻握裝派的特別盤子
你們卡銀的，這個是結婚禮物
離婚時我分到的
對了，小姐們，我現在可是單身喎
等等，你有酬勞，我是來做小區服務的
我還要做200個小時
這個節目才半小時
那我得來400次才夠啊
糟糕，歡迎回來
我們正在宣布由觀眾票選出來
的飛哥與小佛第一季前十名音樂錄像帶
好，你一定要請我吃午餐
現在要欣賞的歌曲是第四名
我有點想他們
就好像我以前從來沒有注意
到另一層關係突然浮現了
Little brother
Even when you
break my toys
You will always
be my little brothers
Cause you'
re younger
We're related
And you're boys
Even when you're
making too much noise
You will
always be my
Little brothers
Cause you'
re younger
We're related
And you're boys
Little brothers
史黛西，你的歌讓我有一點傷心啊
太棒喇，如果我穿襪子嘅話
你一定會感動得掉下來
你真係冇穿襪子？
嗯，目前沒有穿，凱爾
襪子什麼時候好？
就快好了，長官，接下來請欣賞第三名
I can see the
things you're doing
And you think
that I'm naive
But when I get
the goods on you
You should
finally believe
Well she says it'
s all just drama
But every
bubble's got to pop
She's gonna see
just what you're doing
And then you're
finally gonna have to stop
Don't think you'
re gonna win this time
Cause you better
believe I'm gonna drop a dime on you
I'll getcha
I'll get ya
And when I do
You're
gonna be busted
I don't wanna
put the hurt on you
But you better
believe me when I tell you
That I finally
got the dirt on you
You're busted，Yeah
she's finally
gonna see the light
This is how
it's gonna be
When she finds
out that I was always right
You're busted
There's a new
cop on the beat
And I'm
bringing down the heat
My eyes are wide
to all your lies
Cause you're
not that discreet
And I don't care
what you've heard
It's just one
six letter word
It's gonna
set me free
It starts with a B
You're custed
you're busted
I don't wanna
put the hurt on you
But you better
believe me when I tell you
That I finally
got the dirt on you
You're busted
Yeah she's
finally gonna see the light
This is how
it's gonna be
When she finds
out that I was always right
You're busted
太美妙喇，嘿，杜芬舒斯，奇怪喇
你喺度忙什麼呢？
你的末日
媽媽咪啊，凱爾，呼叫米卡泰
他在休息室嚟，長官
好，這樣就簡單多了
請欣賞音樂錄像帶第二名
瓦西尼皇后萬歲
我真不敢相信
Fun playing under
the sun and getting in line
Getting in line '
cause the wet skis running
A backyard beach
Nothing's
that far reach
We got some
backyard beach
You can change
in the broken hut
Drink out
of a coconut
Three games
for a token
But the
rest is free
Beach
a backyard beach
Don't fall
into the breach
Got a
backyard beach
最後的勝利在我的手上了
準備好被科學創造的
音樂錄像帶催眠吧
它會卡在你們的腦子裏，一輩子啊
他很邪惡，按照他的話做
捂住你的耳朵…
不…快給我回去
等等，怎麼回事？
什麼？鴨嘴獸泰瑞？
我發誓所有跟我打過交道的兩棲動物中
就數你最不合作喇
他很邪惡，按照他的話做
成功喇
我成功喇
奧米塔阿泰都進到他們腦子裏喇
我們需要更強嘅東西嚟跟他們對抗
但是，我們…
怎麼？
奧米塔阿泰，現在沒有時間到了
我懂喇
唔好
不能放第一名飛哥和小波的歌
這是加長版，從來沒看過的，不行
各位女士先生，荷葉辣椒，我是飛哥
他是小博，帶來我們的歌，包
chicka，chicka
chewaw
That's what
my baby says
Mow，mow，mow
And my heart
starts pumpin'
Chicka，chicka
chewaw
I'm never
gonna stop
Getcha，getcha，goo
means that
I love you
My baby's got her
own way of talkin'
Whenever she
says something sweet
And she knows
it's my world
she's a rocket
Though my
vocabulary's incomplete
You know it may sound confusingSometimes I wish you'd give it to me straight
But I never feel
like I'm losing
When I take the
time to translate
You know what I'
m talking about
Chicka bow wow
That's what
my baby says
Mow mow mow
And my heart
starts pumpin'
Chicka
chicka chu wop
Never gonna stop
Getcha getcha go
means that I love you
Well I don't
know what to do
I don't
做得好，米卡阿泰，你阻止了杜芬舒斯
拯救了三州地區
還讓今天的十大金曲圓滿結束
謝謝各位的收看，下次再見，説晚安
杜博士
總有一天，我會從籠子裏出去
但你還是叫弗朗西斯